George and Ira Gershwin Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Music (Box 1-63)
  - Music from Shows (Box 1-47)
    - The Barkleys of Broadway [film, 1949] (Box 1)
      - Swing trot
        - Manuscript lead sheet; [1] p., Refrain only, with unused lyric fragments in the hand of IG; Unidentified IG holograph lyric sketches on verso (Box-folder 1/14)
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [3] p. (Box-folder 1/14)
      - Taking no chances on you
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [18] p. (Box-folder 1/15)
      - There is no music
        - Photocopied (ozalid) copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 4 p. (Box-folder 1/16)
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [10] p. (Box-folder 1/16)
      - These days
        - Photocopied (ozalid) copyist manuscript piano-vocal score [no. 1]; 4 p., Correction in an unidentified hand (Box-folder 1/17)
        - Photocopied (ozalid) copyist manuscript piano-vocal score [no. 2]; 4 p., In caption: Rev[ised] (Box-folder 1/17)
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [7] p. and 1 envelope, Correction on p. [2] in the hand of Michael Feinstein; IG holograph lyric revision sketch, ca. 1980, on envelope (Box-folder 1/17)
      - They can’t take that away from me [refrain only], See also "They can't take that away from me" from Shall we dance, Box-Folder 33/14
        - Photocopied (ozalid) copyist manuscript short score; 12 p., Scored by Conrad Salinger (Box-folder 1/18)
      - Weekend in the country
        - Photocopied (ozalid) copyist manuscript short score; 15 p., Scored by Conrad Salinger (Box-folder 1/19)
        - Photocopied (ozalid) copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 6 p. (Box-folder 1/19)
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [3] p. (Box-folder 1/19)
      - The well-known skies of blue
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [14] p. (Box-folder 1/20)
      - You’d be hard to replace
        - Photocopied (ozalid) copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 4 p. (Box-folder 1/21)
        - Sheet music (“Advance artist copy”); [4] p. (Box-folder 1/21)
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [16] p. (Box-folder 1/21)
      - You're my highland fling, Early title for "My one and only highland fling," Box-Folder 1/9
      - Unidentified lyric sketches, IG holograph manuscripts; [5] p. (Box-folder 1/22)
    - Be Yourself [1924] (Box 1)
      - I came here
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 5 p., Extensive emendations in various hands including Albert Sirmay; IG holograph lyric credit in caption (Box-folder 1/23)
      - Money doesn’t mean a thing
        - IG holograph lyric sheet, Verse 2 and part of refrain only (Box-folder 1/24)
      - My heart is yours [unfinished]
        - Typescript lyric sheet; [2] p. (Box-folder 1/25)
      - Not so long ago
        - Manuscript sketch; [2] p., No lyric (Box-folder 1/26)
        - Manuscript lead sheet; [2] p. (Box-folder 1/26)
      - They don’t make ’em that way anymore
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheet (Box-folder 1/27)
      - Uh-uh
        - Manuscript piano-vocal score; [4] p., IG holograph lyric credit in caption (Box-folder 1/28)
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [4] p., Emendations on p. [4] in unidentified hands (Box-folder 1/28)
      - What of it?
        - Typescript lyric sheet (Box-folder 1/29)
      - The wrong thing at the right time
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 5 p. (Box-folder 1/30)
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [5] p. (Box-folder 1/30)
      - List of 21 songs, most by IG and Lewis Gensler
        - IG holograph manuscript, ca. 1925; 1 p. (Box-folder 1/31)
      - List of 18 songs by IG and Lewis Gensler
        - Typescript with annotations by Michael Feinstein; 1 p. (Box-folder 1/31)
      - Title page from IG’s Be Yourself notebook
        - Typescript; 1 p. (Box-folder 1/31)
    - Blue Monday [opera, 1922; revised 1925 and 1953 ] (Box 1)
      - original version, 1922
        - GG holograph manuscript short score; 38 [i.e., 40] p., Partial lyrics only; Presented as part of George White’s Scandals of 1922; withdrawn after one performance (Box-folder Bound)
        - Will Vodery holograph manuscript full score; 156 p., Bound in: original cover with title "135[th] Street" in the hand of GG; Laid in: IG typescript notes [2] p. (Box-folder Bound)
      - revision, 1925
        - Typescript libretto; 4 p., Emendation in the hand of B. G. DeSylva; Laid in: Photocopied holograph letter from DeSylva to GG, 1925 November 25; Laid in: IG holograph notes; [2] p.; Caption title: 135th Street (Box-folder 1/32)
        - Typescript libretto and carbon copy; 4 p. ea., Caption title: 135th Street (Box-folder 1/33)
      - adaptation, 1953
        - Photocopied (ozalid) copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 34 p., Interlinear text in red pencil reflects the original lyrics; Adapted by George Bassman; Caption title: 135th Street blues (Box-folder 1/34)
        - Typescript (mimeograph) libretto; 9 p., Reflects revised libretto for Omnibus Broadcast, 1953 March 29; Laid in: Typescript letter from William Spier to IG, 1953 March 18; Caption title: Blue Monday blues (Box-folder 1/35)
    - Capitol revue [1919] (Box 2)
      - Come to the moon
        - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal score; 3 p., No lyric (Box-folder 2/1)
        - Frank Saddler holograph manuscript full score; 20 p. (Box-folder 2/2)
      - Swanee, See also Sinbad, Box-Folder 35/14
        - Frank Saddler holograph manuscript full score; 21 p. (Box-folder 2/3)
        - Sheet music, 1st edition (with Capitol Theatre cover) (Box-folder 2/4)
        - Photocopied sheet music (French) (Box-folder 2/4)
    - Captain Jinks [1925] (Box 2)
      - You must come over blues
        - Corrected publisher’s final proof; p. 2-5, Laid in: Holograph description by Michael Feinstein, dated 1978 February 16 (Box-folder 2/5)
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [4] p. (Box-folder 2/5)
    - Chopin show [unproduced revue, 1923] (Box 2)
      - Baby me blues
        - IG holograph lyric sheet (Box-folder 2/6)
      - Bittersweet
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [3] p., Possible musical attribution to William Daly in the hand of Michael Feinstein on p. [1] (Box-folder 2/7)
      - Honorable moon
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheet (Box-folder 2/8)
      - The hurdy-gurdy man, See also "A corner of heaven with you," Box-Folder 56/2
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 4 p., No lyric (Box-folder 2/9)
        - Typescript lyric sheet (Box-folder 2/9)
      - Man, the master, See also [Musical sketches], Box-Folder 2/15
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [6] p. (Box-folder 2/10)
      - My all, See also [Musical sketches], Box-Folder 2/15
        - William Daly holograph manuscript piano-vocal score; [2-3] p., Vocal line only; verse incomplete; p. [1] is lost; Early lyric fragment in the hand of IG (Box-folder 2/11)
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [4] p. (Box-folder 2/11)
      - On the wings of romance
        - William Daly holograph manuscript sketch; 1 p., Title and partial lyric in the hand of IG (Box-folder 2/12)
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [4] p. (Box-folder 2/12)
      - Opening
        - William Daly holograph manuscript sketch; [2] p., Partial lyric in the hand of IG; Laid in: Description in the hand of Michael Feinstein (Box-folder 2/13)
      - Someday you'll realize, See also [Musical sketches], Box-Folder 2/15
        - William Daly holograph manuscript piano-vocal score; [4] p., Vocal line only, no lyric (Box-folder 2/14)
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [5] p. (Box-folder 2/14)
      - Musical sketches
        - William Daly holograph manuscript sketches with partial lyrics in the hand of IG; [2] p., p. [1]: My all (refrain only); Etude op. 25, no. 9; Someday you’ll realize (refrain only, no lyric); p. [2]: Someday you’ll realize (verse and refrain); Man, the master (verse and refrain) (Box-folder 2/15)
    - The country girl [film, 1954] (Box 2)
      - Commercials
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [2] p. (Box-folder 2/16)
      - Dissertation on the state of bliss
        - Photocopied (ozalid) copyist piano-vocal score; 5 p. (Box-folder 2/17)
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [6] p. (Box-folder 2/17)
      - The land around us
        - Photocopied (ozalid) copyist piano-vocal score [no. 1]; 8 p., Includes Patter section (Box-folder 2/18)
        - Photocopied (ozalid) copyist piano-vocal score [no. 2]; 6 p. (Box-folder 2/18)
        - Typescript (mimeograph) lyric sheets; 2 p. (Box-folder 2/18)
      - Love and learn, Earlier title "Dissertation on the state of bliss," Box-Folder 2/17
      - The pitchman / It’s mine, it’s yours
        - Photocopied (ozalid) copyist piano-vocal score; 10 p. (Box-folder 2/19)
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [33] p. (Box-folder 2/19)
      - The search is through
        - Photocopied (ozalid) copyist piano-vocal score; [4] p. (Box-folder 2/20)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] p. (Box-folder 2/20)
      - You've got what it takes, Earlier title for "The search is through," Box-Folder 2/20
      - Unidentified lyric sketches
        - IG holograph manuscripts; [3] p. (Box-folder 2/21)
    - Cover girl [film, 1944] (Box 2)
      - Any moment now, See "Long ago (and far away)," Box-Folder 2/23
      - Cover girl
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [11] p. (Box-folder 2/22)
      - Long ago (and far away)
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [5] p., Laid in: 3 discarded lyrics for this melody: Any moment now; [3] p.; Midnight madness; [2] p.; Midnight music; [7] p. (Box-folder 2/23)
      - Make way for tomorrow
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [15] p. (Box-folder 2/24)
      - Midnight madness, See "Long ago (and far away)," Box-Folder 2/23
      - Midnight music, See "Long ago (and far away)," Box-Folder 2/23
      - Put me to the test, See also "Put me to the test" from A damsel in distress, Box-Folder 3/15-17
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [12] p. (Box-folder 2/25)
      - The show must go on
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [14] p. (Box-folder 2/26)
      - Sure thing
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [10] p. (Box-folder 2/27)
      - That girl on the cover, Alternate title for "Cover girl," Box-Folder 2/22
      - That’s the best of all [unfinished?]
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [7] p., Suggestion for lyric alteration on p. [3] in the hand of Jerome Kern (Box-folder 2/28)
      - Time: the present
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [9] p. (Box-folder 2/29)
      - Today's the day (to make way for tomorrow), Alternate title for "Make way for tomorrow," Box-Folder 2/24
      - Tropical night
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [3] p. (Box-folder 2/30)
      - What I love to hear, Early title for "That's the best of all," Box-Folder 2/28
      - Who's complaining?
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [7] p. (Box-folder 2/31)
    - Crazy quilt [unproduced revue?, 1924?] (Box 2)
      - Opening
        - IG holograph lyric sheet; [2] p., This item is not related to Crazy Quilt [revue, 1931 ], Box-Folder 2/33 (Box-folder 2/32)
    - Crazy quilt [revue, 1931] (Box 2)
      - In the merry month of maybe
        - Manuscript piano score; [4] p. (Box-folder 2/33)
        - Typescript lyric sheet, This item is not related to Crazy Quilt [unproduced revue, 1924 ], Box-Folder 2/32 (Box-folder 2/33)
    - A damsel in distress [film, 1937] (Box 3)
      - A foggy day (in London town)
        - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal score; 1, 2, 3 p., Refrain has no lyric (Box-folder 3/1)
        - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal score; 1, 2, 3 p., Photocopied sheet music (German edition) (Box-folder 3/2)
        - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal score; 1, 2, 3 p., Typescript lyric sheet (Box-folder 3/2)
      - I can't be bothered now
        - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal score; 1, 2, 2 p., No lyric (Box-folder 3/3)
        - Typescript lyric sheet (Box-folder 3/4)
      - The jolly tar and the milkmaid
        - Typescript lyric sheet (Box-folder 3/5)
      - The mother of three, Alternate title for "The jolly tar and the milkmaid," Box-Folder 3/5
      - Nice work if you can get it
        - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal score; 1, 5 p., No lyric (Box-folder 3/6)
      - Pay some attention to me [original version, 1928 ]
        - GG holograph manuscript piano sketch; [4] p., In caption in the hand of IG: Old version; [and] Beginning of chorus salvageable (Box-folder 3/7)
        - GG holograph manuscript piano sketch; [4] p. (Box-folder 3/8)
        - 14 copyist manuscript orchestral parts, Laid in: Folder with caricature of GG (Box-folder 3/9)
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheet (Box-folder 3/10)
      - Pay some attention to me [working version, 1937 ]
        - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal score; 2, 3 p., Differs slightly from final version; No lyric (Box-folder 3/11)
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 5 p., Emendations in an unidentified hand; In caption in the hand of IG: 1st version [sic] (Box-folder 3/12)
        - Photocopy [no. 1] of copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 5 p., Extensive emendations in several hands including IG (Box-folder 3/12)
        - Photocopy [no. 2] of copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 5 p., Minor emendations in the hand of IG (Box-folder 3/12)
      - Pay some attention to me [final version, 1937 ]
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; [5] p., Refrain has no lyric (Box-folder 3/13)
        - Photocopy (ozalid) [no. 1] of copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; [5] p. (Box-folder 3/13)
        - Photocopy (ozalid) [no. 2] of copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; [5] p., Chord symbols added to refrain (Box-folder 3/13)
      - Pay some attention to me [working and final versions, 1937 ]
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [15] p. (Box-folder 3/14)
      - Put me to the test, See also "Put me to the test" from Cover girl, Box-Folder 2/25
        - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal score; 1, 4, 3 p., No lyric (Box-folder 3/15)
        - GG holograph manuscript piano sketch; [1] p., Verse only (Box-folder 3/16)
        - Photocopied (ozalid) piano-vocal score; 8 p. (Box-folder 3/17)
        - Corrected 2nd proof of piano-vocal score; p. 2-5, Laid in: Letter from Selma Tamber (Chappell & Co.) to IG, 1937 September 7 (Box-folder 3/17)
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [9] p., Laid in: IG typescript note; [1] p. (Box-folder 3/17)
      - Sing of spring
        - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal score; [3] p., No lyric; Introduction is on p. 3 (Box-folder 3/18)
        - Arranger’s holograph manuscript vocal (SATB) score; 3 p. (Box-folder 3/19)
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 11 p., Incorporates accompaniment from GG manuscript and vocal parts from arranger’s manuscript; Identifying note in caption in the hand of IG (Box-folder 3/19)
        - Typescript lyric sheet (Box-folder 3/19)
      - Stiff upper lip
        - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal score; [1, 2], 2 p., No lyric (Box-folder 3/20)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] p. (Box-folder 3/21)
      - Things are looking up
        - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal score; 2, 3 p., No lyric; GG holograph instruction to copyist on verso of p. 2 concerning p. 1 of refrain (Box-folder 3/22)
        - Typescript/photocopied lyric sheets; [2] p. (Box-folder 3/23)
      - Notes after story conference
        - GG holograph manuscript; [4] p., Laid in: IG holograph note; [1] p. (Box-folder 3/24)
      - Production credits
        - IG holograph manuscript; [1] p. (Box-folder 3/25)
    - The dancing girl [1923] (Box 3)
      - Selection
        - Eugene Platzman (arranger) holograph manuscript (incorporating printed sections) piano score; 20 p. (Box-folder 3/26)
      - That American boy of mine
        - Manuscript piano-vocal score; 5 p. (Box-folder 3/27)
        - Typescript lyric sheet (Box-folder 3/27)
      - That American boy of mine. Patter
        - Copyist manuscript vocal parts; [2] p. ea., 3 copies, one with lyric (Box-folder 3/28)
        - Typescript lyric sheet (Box-folder 3/28)
    - A dangerous maid [1921] (Box 4)
      - Boy wanted
        - Frank Saddler holograph manuscript full score; 32 p., This manuscript was used in London in 1924 for Primrose (Box-folder 4/1)
        - Typescript lyric sheet (original version) (Box-folder 4/1)
        - Typescript lyric sheet (version for Ella Fitzgerald) (Box-folder 4/1)
      - Dancing shoes
        - Sheet music, IG holograph annotation on cover (Box-folder 4/2)
      - Entr’acte I
        - Frank Saddler holograph manuscript full score; 12 p. (Box-folder 4/3)
      - Overture
        - Frank Saddler holograph manuscript full score; 13 p., Laid in: IG typescript description; [1] p. (Box-folder 4/4)
      - The sirens, See also "Four little sirens" from Primrose, Box-Folder 30/20-21
        - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal score; [8] p., Unfinished with partial lyric in the hands of GG and IG; Laid in: IG holograph notes (Box-folder 4/5)
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets (Box-folder 4/6)
      - Some rain must fall
        - Frank Saddler holograph manuscript full score; 22 p. (Box-folder 4/7)
    - Delicious [film, 1931] (Box 4-5)
      - Blah, blah, blah
        - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal score; [1, 2] p., Verse only, no lyric; Introduction in the hand of Albert Sirmay (Box-folder 4/8)
        - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal score; [1, 2] p., Refrain only, no lyric; Laid in: IG typescript description; 1 p. (Box-folder 4/9)
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 5 [i.e., 6] p., Alteration to end of verse in the hand of Albert Sirmay (Box-folder 4/10)
        - Photocopied copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; [2] p., Refrain only, variant lyric (Box-folder 4/10)
        - Corrected publisher’s 2nd proof piano-vocal score; p. 2-5 (Box-folder 4/11)
        - Typescript lyric sheets (including “Russian” refrain); [4] p., Laid in: IG typescript description; 1 p. (Box-folder 4/11)
      - Blah! Blah! Love!, Alternate title for "Blah, blah, blah," Box-Folder 4/8-11
      - Delishious
        - Delishious, Refrain only, no lyric, with added countermelody; Laid in: IG typescript description; 1 p. (Box-folder 4/12)
        - Manuscript piano-vocal score; [5] p., Verse (no lyric) in the hand of Kay Swift; Refrain (with lyric) in the hand of a copyist; Title and music credit in the hand of GG; Cor-rec-ti-ons to lyric in the hand of IG; Introduction and emendations in the hand of Albert Sirmay (Box-folder 4/13)
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 6 p., Emendations in the hand of Albert Sirmay (Box-folder 4/14)
        - Corrected publisher’s 1st proof piano-vocal score; p. 2-5 (Box-folder 4/14)
        - Corrected publisher’s 2nd proof piano-vocal score; p. 2-5 (Box-folder 4/14)
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [3] p., Title on p. [1]: You’re so delishious; Instructions to copyist on p. [1] in the hand of Albert Sirmay (Box-folder 4/14)
      - Delishious [arranged for piano solo]
        - GG holograph manuscript sketch; 1 p., On p. [2] is the opening fragment of a piano solo arrangement of "Nice baby!," Box-Folder 41/36 (Box-folder 4/15)
      - Delishious [arranged for male quartet and piano by Bert Reed]
        - Manuscript (incorporating printed accompaniment) vocal score; 5 p. (Box-folder 4/16)
        - Corrected publisher’s 1st proof; 9 p. (Box-folder 4/16)
      - Dream sequence
        - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal score; 8 p., Lyric and accompaniment omitted on p. 8; Laid in: IG typescript description; 1 p. (Box-folder 4/17)
        - Copyist manuscript piano-conductor score; 9 p., GG holograph signature; Laid in: IG holograph description; 1 p. (Box-folder 4/18)
        - IG typescript scenario/lyric sheets; [4] p. (Box-folder 4/18)
      - Katinkitschka
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; [3] p. (Box-folder 4/19)
        - Photocopied copyist manuscript piano-conductor score; [3] p. (Box-folder 4/19)
        - Corrected publisher’s 2nd proof piano-vocal score; p. 3-5 (Box-folder 4/19)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [3] p. (Box-folder 4/19)
      - Somebody from somewhere
        - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal sketch; [3] p., No lyric; Laid in: IG typescript description; 1 p. (Box-folder 4/20)
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 4 p. (Box-folder 4/21)
        - Photocopied copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; [3] p. (Box-folder 4/21)
        - Publisher’s 2nd proof piano-vocal score; p. 3-5 (Box-folder 4/21)
        - IG typescript lyric sheet (Box-folder 4/21)
      - We’re from the Journal, the Wahrheit, the Telegram, the Times, Alternate title for "Dream sequence," Box-Folder 4/17-18
      - Welcome to the melting pot, Alternate title for "Dream sequence," Box-Folder 4/17-18
      - You started it
        - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal score; [2] p., Verse only, no lyric (Box-folder 4/22)
        - Photocopied GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal score; [2] p., Lyric in ink, in an unknown hand, added ca. 1970s (Box-folder 4/23)
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; [2] p., Refrain only, no lyric (Box-folder 4/23)
        - Photocopied copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; [2] p., Lyric in ink, in an unknown hand, ca. 1970s (Box-folder 4/23)
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [8] p., Laid in: Descriptions in the hands of IG and Michael Feinstein; [2] p. (Box-folder 4/23)
      - Final shooting script
        - Typescript (mimeograph); [8], 98 p. (Box-folder 5/1)
    - Demi-tasse, From the Capitol revue, Box 2
    - Demi tasse revue, From the Capitol revue, Box 2
    - East is west [unproduced, 1928-29] (Box 5)
      - Awake, children, awake, See [Lyric sheets], Box-Folder 5/10
      - Dragon song, See [Lyric sheets], Box-Folder 5/10
      - East is west, See [Lyric sheets], Box-Folder 5/10
      - I speak English now, See [Lyric sheets], Box-Folder 5/10
      - In the Mandarin's orchid garden
        - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal score; 4 p., Unfinished early draft (Box-folder 5/2)
        - Manuscript piano-vocal score in the hands of GG and Kay Swift; 1, 6 p., The ink portion of this score was copied by Swift from GG’s early draft (Box-Folder 5/2); The pencil portion of this score is in the hand of GG (Box-folder 5/3)
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 8 p., The expressive markings in black ink are in the hand of GG; The expressive markings in pencil are in the hand of Albert Sirmay (Box-folder 5/4)
      - Lady of the moon, See also [Lyric sheets], Box-Folder 5/10
        - GG holograph manuscript piano sketch; [2] p. (Box-folder 5/5)
      - Sing-song girl [unfinished], See also [Lyric sheets], Box-Folder 5/10
        - Manuscript piano-vocal score in the hand of Kay Swift; 1 p., No lyric; Caption title in the hand of IG: How sad it is to be a sing song girl (Box-folder 5/6)
        - Photocopy of manuscript piano-vocal score in the hand of Kay Swift [previous entry]; 1 p. (Box-folder 5/6)
        - Manuscript piano score; [3] p., Unidentified fragment on p. [2] (Box-folder 5/6)
      - Under the cinnamon tree, See also [Lyric sheets], Box-Folder 5/10
        - Manuscript piano-vocal sketch, probably in the hand of William Daly; [3] p., No lyric, unfinished? (Box-folder 5/7)
        - Manuscript piano score; [3] p., Unidentified sketch on verso of p. [1] (Box-folder 5/8)
      - We are visitors here [unfinished], See also [Lyric sheets], Box-Folder 5/10; See also "Meadow serenade" from Strike up the band, Box-Folder 37/14